120sports.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy - Stadium

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY (THIS “PRIVACY POLICY”) CAREFULLY BEFORE USING OUR WEBSITE, MOBILE APP OR ANY OTHER 120 SPORTS LLC PRODUCT OR SERVICE.

120 Sports, LLC, doing business as Stadium (“Stadium”), produces and publishes www.watchstadium.com, the Official Website of Stadium (the “Website”), and the Stadium mobile app (the “Mobile App,” and together with the Website, the “Services”). This Privacy Policy describes what information we collect, how we may use that information and the choices we offer for you to manage the information we collect related to your use of our Services. By using the Services, you acknowledge that you have read and understand all the terms and conditions contained herein. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Services or otherwise provide us with any information. By using any of our Services, whether by visiting the Website, downloading or using the Mobile App, voluntarily providing your personally identifiable information to us or otherwise accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy, you consent to the collection and use of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy

**This Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time, so please revisit this page often to remain fully informed of our policies**.

**APPLICABILITY OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the Terms of Use for the Services[LINK]. This Privacy Policy applies only to information submitted or collected online through the Services, and does not apply to information that we may collect offline or other than through the Services. In addition, this Privacy Policy is applicable regardless of the device used to access the Services (e.g., personal computer, mobile device, consumer electronics device, or any other technology or software known today or developed in the future) and to all users of Services. However, certain terms of this Privacy Policy apply only to those who become registered users of the Services.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to information about you collected by any third party services, applications, or websites or advertisements associated with, linked to or otherwise accessible from the Services. **The information collected or received by such third parties, is subject to their own privacy policies** **or practices and under no circumstances is Stadium responsible or liable for the third party’s compliance therewith**. 

  1. Personal Information Collected Via Our Services
  2. How We Use and Share Your Personal Information
  3. Other Information Collected And Shared Within Our Services
  4. Other Circumstances When Your Data May Be Shared
  5. Managing Your Information
  6. Other Information

  1. Personal Information Collected Via Our Services

**Information You Provide.** You may visit and enjoy many elements of our Services without disclosing any personal information about yourself. However, to make use or otherwise take advantage of select, special or enhanced elements of the Services made available from time to time, or to provide you with certain information, you may need to share with us certain personal information. When using certain elements within our Services (e.g., profile creation, promotion registration, making a purchase, or publishing a comment), providing you with certain information about our Services or providing information otherwise of interest to you, the personal information we collect may include, but is not limited to:

  * Full name
  * Email address
  * Password
  * Street address 
  * Zip codes
  * Telephone number(s)
  * Birth date or age
  * Payment card information
  * Location data
  * Contacts (as stored in your wireless device)
  * Other personal data that may be requested from and provided by you, such as gender, personal interests, education and occupation
  * Other information that may be included in the text of any correspondence received from you

If we collect such information, in most instances, the applicable page(s) or location(s) within the Services will specifically ask for the information request or required. In addition to the list above, there may also be opportunities for you to grant permission for use of other of your information in a manner set forth on the applicable page(s) within the Services. See also the section below captioned “Other Information Collected and Shared Within Our Services.”

  2. How We Use and Share Your Personal Information

We collect, retain, and use personal information you provide to us for legitimate business purposes only. If you submit personal information to us, or to any third party acting on our behalf, we may use and share your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy or as disclosed when you submit your information. We will not sell, lease, publish or share your personal information with or to anyone else, except as set forth in this Privacy Policy or as so disclosed. We may use and share your personal information as follows:

  * Use your information to provide you with information regarding the services, products and features available through the Services;
  * Use your information to establish you as a registered user and provide the services, products or features (including various content) you’ve requested or provide you with offers or promotions (e.g., a sweepstakes, fantasy game, subscription to goods or services, etc.), including the results thereof, or add you to our email or postal mail list;
  * Use your information to address any query, request or other issues raised in email correspondence to us;
  * Share your information with certain third parties, including service providers, sponsors and promotional partners, so they may help us provide services, offers, promotions or other information or content of interest to you, which you’ve requested or otherwise in accordance with the applicable rules of a promotion or terms presented at the time you submit personal information, so the third party can administer the promotion, send you offers or content or add you to their email or postal mailing list;
  * Share your information with vendors or service providers in connection with any purchase ofgoods and services; or 
  * Use and share your information with permission from you.

  3. Other Information Collected, Used And Shared Within Our Services

  * _Our Cookies and Web Beacons_

We use and permit automatic information and data collection methods, such as cookies (small amounts of data which include a unique string of characters sent to your browser or application from a website’s computers and stored on your computer’s or device’s hard drive), web beacons (technology used to track activity, also known as pixel tags) or similar technologies, alone or in combination with personally identifiable information you choose to provide us. Examples of the information we collect and analyze using such methods include, but is not limited to: personal information as authorized by you, the Internet protocol address used to connect your computer or device to the Internet; email address; login name and password; operating system and browser type, version and computer or device platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locator clickstream to, on and from our Services, including date and time; and products you viewed, searched, downloaded or streamed.. In addition, we use log files and software tools to measure and collect Website session information, including how many “hits” a particular web page is getting (a.k.a. “click-through data”), the dates and times that you use the Services, the pages you visit and the amount of time spent on specific pages, page response times, download errors, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from a page. 

We use and may allow certain third parties, such as those who provide services associated with our Services, to access these automatic data collection methods and use such automatically collected information and data to operate and improve our services (including our benefits offerings); to operate or improve the Services; enable you to use a “shopping cart” while using our Services, to store your preferences and to improve, deliver and customize our Services’ content and offerings; to monitor visitor traffic patterns and usage of the Services in order to assess overall Website activity, track interest in particular portions of our Website and troubleshoot technical concerns; to personalize your use of the Services, including to allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you see on the Services; to gather and analyze data for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly offer a better experience, drive user growth and improve the Services; to track content access, downloads and streams for the purpose of paying royalties and license fees to third-party content providers; and for identification and security purposes.

  * _Mobile App and Device Information_

When you download or use the Mobile App, it may automatically collect certain information which may be considered personally identifiable, such as your mobile device’s unique device ID, the IP address of your mobile device and your device’s proprietary advertising identifier, as well as information relating to how you use the Mobile App, such as the content you view, ads you click, and purchases you make. In addition, when you download or use the Mobile App, we will ask for permission to access or to provide to you additional information, including the right to provide “push” notifications. If you permit the Mobile App to use location services (also known as global positioning system or “GPS”), depending on the settings on your mobile device, we may collect the precise or general location information provided by your device.

In addition, to the other uses of information as explained in this section captioned “How We Use and Share Your Personal Information,” information collected from the Mobile App may be used to facilitate the functionality of our Mobile App and deliver valuable, entertaining content and advertising to you. We may collect your device’s location in order to show you offers or features available near you, to deliver more relevant information and ads. We may combine data we collect through our Mobile App with other information we hold about you so that we can personalize or improve the relevance and quality of the services we provide you.

  * _Third Party Cookies and Web Beacons; Network Advertisers_

We allow select third parties, such as those who deliver advertisements, content, social networking or provide other services associated with our Services, to set cookies, web beacons or similar technologies in certain locations within the Services or certain emails sent by us. Third party companies that manage and deliver advertisements to websites and applications such as ours are commonly referred to as “network advertisers.” A permitted network advertiser may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to collect information about your interaction with our Services as well as with third party websites in order to tailor certain advertisements and content delivered within our Services and on other websites within such network advertiser’s ad network. Advertisers’ use of cookies and similar technologies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy. You may elect to opt out of targeted behavioral advertising from many major third party network advertisers by [clicking here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). If you would like to obtain more information about common industry practices of network advertisers or make choices about their use of your information or find additional opt-out tools operated by advertising industry associations encompassing even more network advertisers, please [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/). 

  * _Third Party Analytics Providers_

We also use third party analytics service providers to provide us or third parties with information about the viewing of ads on our Services and third party websites or applications, and to better understand our users’ use of our Services. We and third-party vendors use first-party cookies and third-party cookies together to report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our Services.

  * _Social Networking_

When using our Services or when using certain third party social networking services (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, Google +) (each and collectively, a “Social Network”), you may have the option to connect your information and activity on the Services with your Social Network information and activity. If you authorize such a connection, you permit us to share or publish information about your activity on our Services with that Social Network and its users and to access certain of your Social Network information, as disclosed by you at the time you consent to the connection. Information we may share with a Social Network may include, but is not limited to: technical information about your Services activity, your Services comments or the videos you watch on our Services. Information we may access about you, with your consent (either through your privacy settings on the Social Network or otherwise), from a Social Network may include, but is not limited to, your basic Social Network information, your location data, your list of contacts, friends or followers, and certain of your activities on the Social Network. If you permit a connection between a Social Network and our Services, we (and that Social Network) may be able to identify you and to associate information received pursuant to the connection with information we already have about you. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with the privacy policy and privacy control options of any Social Network with which you choose to share information or connect to our Services.

  4. Other Circumstances When Your Data May Be Shared

  * _Aggregated Demographic Information_

We may share aggregated demographic and statistical information regarding the visitors to the Website, Mobile App, traffic patterns, and Services usage with third parties, including our partners, affiliates or advertisers. This information is not linked to personal information that can identify you or another individual person. 

  * _Business Transfers_

As time passes, Stadium (or portions thereof) may be sold along with its assets, or other corporate transactions may occur. In such a case, our customer information may be one of the business assets we transfer.

  * _Disclosure for Legal Purposes_

We may be required to share your personal and non-personal information pursuant to judicial or governmental subpoenas, warrants or orders. If we are required to do so, we will, of course, obey the law. In addition, notwithstanding any term to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, we reserve the right to use, disclose or share your personal and non-personal information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of Terms of Use of any of our Services or as required by law. 

  5. Managing Your Information

You have certain choices about the information we collect. When you are asked to provide information, you may decline; but if you choose not to provide information that is necessary to provide a service or feature, you may not be able to use that service or feature. If and to the extent we make available means for you to register, make a purchase, or otherwise require that you submit personal information, it may be possible for you to choose and control certain information you provide about yourself and to update and remove the information you provide.

Certain information, including cookie based information, is automatically collected via our Services. If you do not wish to provide certain information necessary for enhanced functionality or content on our Services, please do not use such functionality or content. In addition, if you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows a user to accept or reject most cookies. Certain cookies that are set when some video products are accessed on our Website, called local shared objects or Flash cookies, may not be managed using the settings in your web browser. Information on managing, accepting and rejecting these cookies is available from Adobe on the [Adobe website](http://www.adobe.com/). If you set your browser or Adobe Flash options not to accept cookies or local shared objects, you may not be able to take advantage of certain Services.

You can deactivate location services and GPS functionality on your mobile device or remove the permission for the Mobile App to access location services. Please refer to your device manufacturer or operating system instructions for instructions on how to do this. The Mobile App may store certain information locally on your device depending on how you use it. Refer to your device settings for information regarding deletion of locally stored data. 

Remember that when you share information publicly online, it may be indexable by search engines or recorded by others, and any search engine index or record of your information may persist after you delete the information at the original source.

_Communications Opt-Out_. You may opt out of receiving materials or other communications from us by following the opt-out link or other unsubscribe instructions provided in any email received, or by contacting us as provided at the end of this Privacy Policy. You may also be able to customize the communications you receive from us through preferences in your user account if you have registered for such an account, such as by activating or deactivating push notifications through your mobile device’s settings. If you do business with us, you may not opt out of notifications related to those business transactions (e.g., e-commerce). 

  6. Other Information

_No Spyware or Adware_

We do not install any spyware or adware in connection with our Services, or distribute any commercial message, or authorize any third party to distribute any commercial message, by means of spyware or adware. “Spyware” or “adware” is any software which has been downloaded to or installed on an Internet user’s computer or device, without the user’s actual consent, and facilitates the distribution of any commercial message to the user. If you feel you may have spyware from another company installed on your machine, there are various anti-spyware/adware software applications available on the Internet to identify if this has occurred.

_Do Not Track_

We do not engage in the collection of personal information about your online activities over time and across third party websites or online services. Accordingly, we do not currently process or comply with any web browser’s “do not track” (DNT) signal or other mechanisms that provide consumers with the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personal information about your online activities over time and across third party websites. However, as noted in the section captioned “Third Party Cookies and Web Beacons; Network Advertisers,” we allow some advertisers and other third party companies to collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit our Website or use the Mobile App which, through “tracking technologies,” can be combined with non-personally identifiable information during your visits to other websites or when you use other mobile applications in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or a third party web beacon to collect this information.

_Our Security Practices_

Because security is important to both Stadium and you, we maintain physical, electronic and administrative safeguards designed to ensure the security of our systems and protect your personal information from unauthorized or inappropriate access. In this regard, we use industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions and store personal information in secure datacenters. It is important to note that no method of safeguarding information is 100% secure. While we try to ensure the protection of your personal information, we cannot guarantee that our safeguards will be effective or sufficient. In addition, you should be aware that Internet data transmission is not always secure and we cannot warrant that information you transmit utilizing the Services is secure. 

_Links and Third Party Sweepstakes or Contests_

Our Services contain links to other websites and products produced by Stadium and to websites and products operated by unrelated third parties. In addition, if you click on an advertisement within our Services, you may be directed to a web page within our Services or to a third-party website or product. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party websites or products, and we encourage you to read the privacy policies of every website and product that collects personally identifiable information from you. This Privacy Policy applies only to our Services, unless you are notified otherwise upon accessing any third party website or product, in which case the terms and conditions set forth in such notification will apply.

Sometimes sweepstakes or contests found through the Services are hosted or operated by a third-party advertiser or sponsor. In those cases where we are not the sponsor, operator or host of a sweepstakes or contest, we may have no control over the information collected and, accordingly, we encourage you to review the official rules of the sweepstakes or contest as well as the advertiser’s or sponsor’s privacy policy applicable to the sweepstakes or contest before participating.

_Your California Privacy Rights_

If you are a resident of California, pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, you may request information regarding our disclosure of your personal information to a third party for that party’s direct marketing purposes. Any such disclosure made to a third party by us would be otherwise in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. To make such a request please send an email to legal@watchstadium.com or write to us at: 122 North Aberdeen, Chicago, IL 60607.

_Special Rules For Children_

Because of federal law, we are not permitted to knowingly collect any personal information from a child under the age of thirteen without the consent of that child’s parent or guardian. To the extent that any personal information from children under the age of thirteen is inadvertently collected, the statements in this Privacy Policy about our collection and use of personal information also apply to our treatment of that personal information.  If a child who we know to be under the age of thirteen and for whom we have not received parental consent attempts to utilize a service on our Services which is not available to children, he/she will not be able to access it and may receive a message which relays that he/she is not eligible for such feature.

_International Use_

Your personal information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or where we have engaged a service provider, and by your use of the Services you acknowledge that we may transfer information to countries outside of your country of residence, which may have different data protection rules than in your country.  

_Contact Us Regarding Privacy_

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at: 

Stadium   
Attention: Privacy Administrator  
122 North Aberdeen  
Chicago, Illinois 60607

Or send an email to: [legal@watchstadium.com ](mailto:legal@watchstadium.com)

  * _Notification of Changes_

If we make an important change to this Privacy Policy, we will post a notification and link on our Website’s homepage so that you may review the updated policy.

_Last updated and effective date: July 1, 2017_
